Harvard University, Graduate School of Design. The GSD History Collection, Administrative Affairs: An Inventory
Harvard University, Graduate School of Design. The GSD History Collection, Administrative Affairs: An Inventory
- Series B: Harvard University GSD, Administrative Affairs: External Relations, / Date(s): 1960-2008 (inclusive) -- 1960-1989 (bulk); B000; / Quantity: 5 boxes / Dimensions: 5 linear ft. / Medium: varies / Support: varies
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1970; Folder: BC059; / Quantity: 4 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Development papers, originally labeled "Printed Matter, 1969-1970." Listing of students from the GSD that were registered with the HGSDA Placement Office, 1970.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1969-1970; Folder: BC060; / Quantity: 14 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Development papers, originally labeled "Printed Matter, 1969-1970." Includes forms sent to firms by the HGSDA Placement Office for student job placements. Also include prospectus on appointment of Kilbridge as dean of the GSD, invitation cards to the ground-breaking ceremony for George Gund Hall, and booklet with directory assistance for the GSD (when located at Robinson Hall and offices at Hunt Hall).
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1969-1970; Folder: BC061; / Quantity: 69 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print; typescript; mimeograph copies / Support: paper
    Note: Development papers, originally labeled "Printed Matter, 1969-1970." File includes several papers / documents: Elections of Departmental Representatives and a General Council of the Graduate School of Design, Graduate School of Design General Council and Departmental Representatives, Address to the General Forum of the Harvard Graduate School of Design by Maurice Kilbridge, and Student Information and Registration Bulletin for the Academic Year 1969-1970.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1972-1973; Folder: BC062; / Quantity: 20 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print; typescript / Support: paper
    Note: Development papers, originally labeled "Printed Matter, 1972-1973." Includes materials related to the dedication of Gund Hall: HGSDA Dedication Review, Gund Hall Dedication. October 12-13, 1972 (program of events), and request for support for an acquisitions fund for the Frances Loeb Library (signed by Maurice Kilbridge and Caroline Shillaber). Also includes information on applications to the Wheelwright Fellowship, and the HGSD Work-Study Program. There is also a letter from Kilbridge to alumnae in relation to "a concerted effort by the GSD to increase the number of women on its faculty" (includes a questionnaire).
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1972-1973; Folder: BC063; / Quantity: 10 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 8-1/2" x 4"; 7" x 5" / Medium: print; typescript / Support: paper
    Note: Development papers, originally labeled "Printed Matter, 1972-1973." Includes brochures / prospectuses of the -at the time- recently built Gund Hall, Invitation from Harvard President Derek Bok for a dinner in honor of the Donors to George Gund Hall.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1970-1971; Folder: BC064; / Quantity: 35 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print; typescript / Support: paper
    Note: Development papers, originally labeled "Printed Matter, 1970-1971." Announcements of alumni events, faculty appointments, Council elections, reprint of a writing on the Frances Loeb Library by Caroline Shillaber, and correspondence related to pledges to the GSD's capital campaign.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1970-1971; Folder: BC065; / Quantity: 46 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print; typescript / Support: paper
    Note: Development papers, originally labeled "Printed Matter, 1970-1971." Includes information about the job placement assistance program at the GSD, a booklet entitled Harvard and Money: a Memorandum on Issues and Choices (November 1970), correspondence about fundraising pledges for the construction of Gund Hall (photograph of Gund Hall under construction included in the stationery, explanation of the Wheelwright Fellowship, among other announcements and communications with alumni/ae.
    Note: Also includes correspondence to alumni/ae related to the decision of the Harvard Corporation that the "Master in Architecture henceforth be awarded as the first degree in architecture and that it be made available retroactively, on application, to B.Arch. graduates of the school" (as of May 4, 1970).
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1973-1974; Folder: BC066; / Quantity: 23 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print; typescript / Support: paper
    Note: Development papers, originally labeled "Printed Matter, 1973-1974." Includes correspondence with alumni with explanation of and application form for the Wheelwright Travelling Fellowship, letter from George Anselevicius upon being appointed Chairman of the Department of Architecture, and ballots for Council of the HGSDA.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1971-1972; Folder: BC067; / Quantity: 33 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print; typescript / Support: paper
    Note: Development papers, originally labeled "Printed Matter, 1971-1972." Information about continuing education courses, intention of creating a work-study program, fundraising appeal for the library, back-to-school letter, explanation of the Wheelwright Travelling Fellowship, effort to improve the status of women in the school ("we want especially to attract more qualified women students and to increase the number of women on the faculty"), and press release relative grievances lodged against Maurice Kilbridge by Professors Isaacs, Nash, and Vigier (includes press release and statement by Kilbridge).
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1970-1971; Folder: BC068; / Quantity: 28 items / Dimensions: 5-1/2" x 8-1/2" / Medium: print; typescript / Support: paper
    Note: Development papers, originally labeled "Printed Matter, 1970-1971." Includes explanation of Wheelwright Travelling Fellowship, brochure and recommendation form for the Loeb Fellowship Program, questionnaire for and about HGSDA News, and ballots for HGSDA Council.
    Note: Also includes Program of Proceedings for Gund Hall opening/dedication day (with drawing of Gund Hall in yellow, orange, and purple). The program is tied with yellow yarn.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1973; Folder: BC069; / Quantity: 15 items / Dimensions: 17" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Several copies of HGSD News, October 1973.
    Note: Includes obituary of Shadrach Woods. Also includes section on the "Demise of Hunt Hall" (when it was demolished).
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1973; Folder: BC070; / Quantity: 20 items / Dimensions: 17" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Several copies of HGSD News, May 1973.
    Note: Includes note on John Andrews, architect of Gund Hall.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1973; Folder: BC071; / Quantity: 6 items / Dimensions: 17" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Several copies of HGSD News, March 1973.
    Note: Includes note on the Loeb Fellowship Program.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1973; Folder: BC072; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 17" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Copy of HGSD News, January 1973.
    Note: Gund Hall dedication issue, with specific notes on the dedication of Frances L. Loeb Library, Piper Auditorium, and Le Corbusier Collection.
    Note: Also includes note on the 9th annual Gropius Lecture.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1972; Folder: BC073; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Newsletter Harvard Graduate School of Design, Spring 1972. Most of the GSD newsletters have to do with alumni news and school news.
    Note: Includes section on "Urban Design Education: Origin, Scope, and Direction" by Michael Brammah.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1971; Folder: BC074; / Quantity: 5 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: HGSDA News, April 1971.
    Note: Includes section on the Loeb Fellowship Program, and another on the Frances Loeb Library (Le Corbusier Collection and Cluny Collection).
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1971; Folder: BC075; / Quantity: 5 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: HGSDA News, April 1971. See BC074.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1972; Folder: BC076; / Quantity: 6 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Newsletter Harvard Graduate School of Design, Summer 1972.
    Note: Includes section on "Interdisciplinary Collaboration."
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1972; Folder: BC077; / Quantity: 5 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Newsletter Harvard Graduate School of Design, Summer 1972. See BC076.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1969; Folder: BC078; / Quantity: 8 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: HGSDA News, No.1, 1969. Includes photographs and chronological summary of action by the Students for a Democratic Society to occupy University Hall and present their demands to President Nathan Pusey.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1969; Folder: BC079; / Quantity: 8 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: HGSDA News, No.1, 1969. See BC078.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1969; Folder: BC080; / Quantity: 9 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1968-1970; Folder: BC081; / Quantity: 13 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 6" x 9" / Medium: print; ink / Support: paper
    Note: Lists and bills related to costs of HGSDA News, 1968-1970.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1969; Folder: BC082; / Quantity: 4 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: ink / Support: paper
    Note: Other costs of HGSDA.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1968; Folder: BC083; / Quantity: 15 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript; copies / Support: paper
    Note: Specifications for typographer and printer of the HGSDA News, No. 4, 1968.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1968; Folder: BC084; / Quantity: 6 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript; print / Support: paper
    Note: Paper samples and typeface samples for HGSDA News.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1969; Folder: BC085; / Quantity: 17 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript; print / Support: paper
    Note: Specifications for typographer, printer, and camerastat for the HGSDA News, No. 1-3, 1969.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1969; Folder: BC086; / Quantity: 9 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript; print / Support: paper
    Note: Other specifications for HGSDA.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1969; Folder: BC087; / Quantity: 27 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript; print / Support: paper
    Note: More specifications for HGSDA.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1968-1969; Folder: BC088; / Quantity: 41 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Technical sources for publications.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1968-1969; Folder: BC089; / Quantity: 4 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Reproduction proofs of typeface for envelopes, letterhead, etc.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1968; Folder: BC090; / Quantity: 10 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Memorandum about copyright policy within Harvard University.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1968; Folder: BC091; / Quantity: 45 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: mimeograph / Support: paper
    Note: Several copies of forms for publication notices to be included in the Harvard Gazette.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1966-1969; Folder: BC092; / Quantity: 51 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript / Support: paper
    Note: Correspondence from readers and editors of GSD publications. One from Caroline Shillaber to Professor William Doebele in relation to possible publication projects.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1968-1969; Folder: BC093; / Quantity: 28 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript; ink / Support: paper
    Note: Forms and newsletter distribution lists.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1966; Folder: BC094; / Quantity: 28 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript; ink / Support: paper
    Note: Mailing lists, and memo on press releases within the university. Includes prospectus on Harvard University Gazette, first expanded release in 1969.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1966; Folder: BC095; / Quantity: 5 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: ink / Support: paper
    Note: Contact information for issues related to photos for HGSDA publications.
    Note:
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1970; Folder: BC096; / Quantity: 5 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 4" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: File includes four identical copies of brochures from the GSD about the Program in Advanced Environmental Studies, recently instituted at the time as an interdisciplinary program.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1969; Folder: BC097; / Quantity: 6 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 4" / Medium: typescript / Support: paper
    Note: Documents front pages (documents missing) and other materials related to a two-day alumni gathering, ca. 1969.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1971; Folder: BC098; / Quantity: 20 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 4" / Medium: typescript / Support: paper
    Note: Questionnaire (with responses) sent out by the HGSDA to reevaluate the importance and effectiveness of the HGSDA News. See folders BC098 through BC103.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1969; Folder: BC099; / Quantity: 20 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 4" / Medium: typescript / Support: paper
    Note: Questionnaire (with responses) sent out by the HGSDA to reevaluate the importance and effectiveness of the HGSDA News. See BC098.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1969; Folder: BC100; / Quantity: 20 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 4" / Medium: typescript / Support: paper
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1969; Folder: BC101; / Quantity: 20 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 4" / Medium: typescript / Support: paper
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1969; Folder: BC102; / Quantity: 20 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 4" / Medium: typescript / Support: paper
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations, / Date(s): 1969; Folder: BC103; / Quantity: 21 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 4" / Medium: typescript / Support: paper
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations -- Alumni Events: Atlanta, / Date(s): 1991; Folder: BC104; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript / Support: paper
    Note: Correspondence to Mack Scogin in relation to a possible alumni event in Atlanta and possible sources of funding for CAD-related efforts at the GSD.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations -- Alumni Events: New England Regional, / Date(s): 1989; Folder: BC105; / Quantity: 25 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 4" x 9-1/2" / Medium: typescript; print / Support: paper
    Note: Correspondence and brochures about the organization of several alumni events in the New England region.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations -- Alumni Events: Chicago, / Date(s): 1986-1995; Folder: BC106; / Quantity: 10 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 7" x 5" / Medium: typescript; print / Support: paper
    Note: Correspondence and cards about the organization of alumni events in Chicago.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations -- Alumni Events: Florida Regional, / Date(s): 1985-1989; Folder: BC107; / Quantity: 5 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 7" x 5" / Medium: typescript; print / Support: paper
    Note: Correspondence and cards about the organization of alumni events in Florida.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations -- Alumni Events: Houston, / Date(s): 1990-1991; Folder: BC108; / Quantity: 6 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript / Support: paper
    Note: Correspondence about the organization of alumni events in Houston during an AIA Convention
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations -- Alumni Events: Italy, / Date(s): 1989; Folder: BC109; / Quantity: 5 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript / Support: paper
    Note: Correspondence about the organization of alumni events in Italy.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations -- Alumni Events: London, / Date(s): 1991; Folder: BC110; / Quantity: 5 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript / Support: paper
    Note: List of people attending an alumni event in London.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations -- Alumni Events: London, / Date(s): 1990; Folder: BC111; / Quantity: 62 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript; print b&w photographs / Support: paper
    Note: Correspondence and other paperwork (lists, contact information) related to alumni events in London. Some black-and-white photographs and contacts for the event are included.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations -- Alumni Events: London, / Date(s): 1990; Folder: BC112; / Quantity: 4 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 4" / Medium: typescript; print; photographs / Support: paper
    Note: Envelopes with photographs, business cards, attendance lists, and contacts of an alumni event in London.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations -- Alumni Events: London, / Date(s): 1990-1991; Folder: BC113; / Quantity: 69 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript; print / Support: paper
    Note: Correspondence and other organizational files related to alumni events in London.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations -- Alumni Events: Los Angeles, / Date(s): 1987-1992; Folder: BC114; / Quantity: 16 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript; print / Support: paper
    Note: Correspondence and other organizational files related to alumni events in Los Angeles.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations -- Alumni Events: Los Angeles, / Date(s): 1990; Folder: BC115; / Quantity: 72 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 5" x 7" / Medium: copies; print / Support: paper
    Note: Xerographic copies of photographs, and cards related to alumni events in Los Angeles. Among speakers: Ricardo Legorreta, Laurie Olin, and John McAlister (Pershing Square Property President).
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations -- Alumni Events: Southern California, / Date(s): 1992; Folder: BC116; / Quantity: 65 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript / Support: paper
    Note: Correspondence and other organizational files related to alumni events in Southern California.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations -- Alumni Events: Middle East, / Date(s): 1991; Folder: BC117; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript / Support: paper
    Note: Correspondence related fundraising and/or alumni events in the Middle East.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations -- Alumni Events: New York, / Date(s): 1987-1993; Folder: BC118; / Quantity: 13 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 8-1/2" x 5" / Medium: typescript; print / Support: paper
    Note: Correspondence related to the organization and invitation to an alumni event in New York, with the following honorary speakers: Edward Larrabee Barnes, Philip Johnson, I.M. Pei, Paul Rudolph.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations -- Alumni Events: San Francisco, / Date(s): 1986-1991; Folder: BC119; / Quantity: 18 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 5" x 7"; 14" x 8-1/2" / Medium: typescript; print / Support: paper
    Note: Several cards and correspondence related to alumni events in San Francisco.
    Note: Includes small poster of A Celebration and Exploration, with speakers: Garret Eckbo, Richard Haag, Lawrence Halprin, and Hideo Sasaki. The text of the introduction by Melanie Simo is also included: "Eckbo, Halprin, Sasaki, Haag: a Retrospective." And "Reflections" by Peter Walker
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations -- Alumni Events: Seattle Regional, / Date(s): 1991; Folder: BC120; / Quantity: 22 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 5" x 7" / Medium: typescript; print / Support: paper
    Note: Correspondence and cards related to alumni events in Seattle. Includes participants list.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations -- Alumni Events: Tokyo, / Date(s): 1994; Folder: BC121; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript / Support: paper
    Note: List of attendants to an alumni event in Tokyo.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations -- Alumni Events: Toronto, / Date(s): 1989-1993; Folder: BC122; / Quantity: 23 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript / Support: paper
    Note: Correspondence and lists for alumni events in Toronto.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations -- Alumni Events: Texas, / Date(s): 1987-1989; Folder: BC123; / Quantity: 40 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript; print / Support: paper
    Note: Correspondence and cards related to alumni events in Texas (Houston and Dallas).
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations -- Alumni Events: Washington DC, / Date(s): 1994; Folder: BC124; / Quantity: 40 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: typescript / Support: paper
    Note: Correspondence and lists of attendees to alumni events in Washington D.C.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations -- Alumni Events: Washington DC, / Date(s): 1986-1991; Folder: BC125; / Quantity: 11 items / Dimensions: 4" x 6"; 4" x 9" / Medium: typescript; print / Support: paper
    Note: Cards for alumni events in Washington DC. Includes brochures of area museums.
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations -- Posters, / Date(s): 1993-1998; Folder: BC126; / Quantity: 14 items / Dimensions: 16" x 8-1/2"; 10-1/2" x 6"; 6" x 4" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Cards and posters for several events organized by the GSD: "Environmental Regulation in an Age of Property Rights"; "Manufactured Sites"; "Architecture or Segregation"; "The New Inside the New: Latin American Architecture and Urbanism, and the Crisis of the International Style, 1937-1954"; "Berlin: Fashioning a National Capital at the End of the Twentieth Century"; "Constructs and Responsibilities in Architectural Practices: a Critical Exploration; and "Center and Edges of Practice."
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations -- Posters, / Date(s): 1990-1997; Folder: BC127; / Quantity: 15 items / Dimensions: 7" x 5"; 9" x 6"; 8-1/2" x 8-1/2"; 10" x 7-1/2" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Cards and posters for several events organized by the GSD: "Landscape Architecture, Social Ideology and the Politics of Place"; "Reconceptualizing the Modern: Architectural Culture, 1943-1968"; "Exploring New Urbanism"; "The Environment, Sustainable Development and Design"; "Florence Cathedral in the Renaissance: Around and Above the High Altar"; "A Historical and Practical Introduction to the Art of Mosaic"; "Symposium on Architectural Practices"; "Center and Edges of Practice"; "Constructs and Responsibilities in Architectural Practices: a Critical Exploration"; "Dan Kiley: The First Two Decades."
  - Subseries BC: Alumni Relations -- Alumni Reunions, / Date(s): 2000; Folder: BC128; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Spiral bound Class of 1950, 50th Reunion booklet. Includes alumni profiles and directory.